<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>

	<DankPyon_GameStart_TavernStart>The walls of a city were never reassuring. Neither was the bustle of urban life that could suck the soul out of a lich, given time.\nWhat opportunities you could find were unsuitable for you for so many, many reasons: one, a lack of fitness, while another a lack of heartlessness.\n\nIt was this environment that told you to leave, with but raw materials and simple tools to fashion your dream.\nFor you aspired to a home out in the wilderness, a hearth that could welcome many a weary and worn traveler.\nRogue or hero, it would shelter them all.\n\nWith any hope comes risk, and this was one you could not ignore.\nReports from the local garrison indicated an increased bandit presence, and crime was on the rise.\nEven with the most careful preparations, a criminal would most likely follow your trail.\n\nBut you took the leap of faith, and stepped across the threshold of the city.\nWith wilderness ahead and treachery behind, you march away.\n\nOptimism and worry cloud your brow.</DankPyon_GameStart_TavernStart>
	
	<DankPyon_GameStart_LoneWolfStart>One year’s service—that was the deal.\nThe lord whom I followed attempted many times to keep my sword by his side, but a deal is a deal and after one year, I swore no further oaths.\nAs I traverse the wooded hills, I wonder to myself whether the decision was correct.\n\nI may have hoarded wealth, but bandits roam the countryside, and should my campfire not betray me, hungry beasts and monsters hidden in the dark eye me all the same.\nI often wonder if I should have allowed my lord to wield me as his sword again, but I also know that in doing so, I would forgo my freedom.\n\nSo, after retrieving my silver, I march with no end in sight.\nPerhaps I will be so lucky as to find a homestead, build a hall, and gather my own household warriors.\nBut the long-term goal seemed so far away, as I must focus on my foremost problems.\n\nFirst, I must survive.</DankPyon_GameStart_LoneWolfStart>
	
	<DankPyon_GameStart_MercenaryStart>Your lord, to whom you and your comrades remained forever loyal as long as there is money, fell at a concise battle. Free of your oath, your band of mercenaries departed to neighboring towns and cities in search of opportunity for silver and reputation but were disappointed to find peace-laden settlements, full of bounties fit for a dayt</DankPyon_GameStart_MercenaryStart>
	
	
	
</LanguageData>